A Guide to the Armistead Boothe Papers, 1803-1990
Alexandria Library, Local History/Special Collections
- Program: Dedication of the Armistead Boothe addition to Bishop Payne Library, Virginia Theological Seminary, November 11, 1980. (Box-folder 173C:38)
- An Uncommon Law Marriage, article re: merger of two law firms, from New Dominion, Spring 1987. (Box-folder 173C:39)
- Sons of the Revolution membership certificate and card for Gardner L. Boothe, 1928. (Box-folder 173C:40)
- Miscellaneous Carr family information. (Box-folder 173C:41)
- Genealogical information on Thoroughgood family. (Box-folder 173C:42)
- Photographs. (Box-folder 173C:43)